# YICHI ZHANG

 $+1(734)800-6032 \diamond$  yichiz@umich.edu  $\diamond$  Website: https://yichiz97.github.io/4352 North Quad, 510 State St., Ann Arbor, MI 48109, U.S.A.

#### RESEARCH INTERESTS

Information elicitation, mechanism design, multi-agent systems, incentive-aware learning and decision making, problems at the interface of AI and economics. Applications of interest include crowdsourcing, peer review, peer grading, recommender systems, and generative AI. My recent research interest is centered around utilizing large language models to elicit and aggregate text-based human responses, e.g. in peer review.

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (Umich)

Sep 2019 - Present

- Ph.D. in School of Information
- Advisor: Grant Schoenebeck
- Thesis: Incentive Design for Data-driven Systems: Effort and Information Elicitation

#### Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU)

Aug 2015 - Jun 2019

- B.S. in Electronic Science and Engineering
- Advisor: Xinbing Wang and Luoyi Fu

#### WORKING EXPERIENCES

| University of Michigan, School of Information<br>Research Assistant, Useful Theory Innovation Lab | Sep 2019 - Present  |
|---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------|---------------------|
| UCLA, Department of Computer Science<br>Research Intern, working with Mario Gerla                 | Jul 2018 - Sep 2018 |

YITUTech
Algorithm Engineer Intern
Feb 2019 - May 2019

# SUBMISSIONS UNDER REVIEW

Understanding When Peer Grades (Definitely) Outperform Instructor Grades Noah Burrell, Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

Spot Check Equivalence: a Metric of an Information Elicitation Mechanism's Motivational Proficiency

Shengwei Xu, Grant Schoenebeck, Yichi Zhang and Paul Resnick

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

# Eliciting Honest Information From Authors Using Sequential Review

Yichi Zhang, Grant Schoenebeck and Weijie Su

In Proceedings of the 38th Annual AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2024)
[https://arxiv.org/abs/2311.14619]

# Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference (WWW 2023)
[https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583292]

# High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference (WWW 2023)
[https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583334]

# A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

**Yichi Zhang**, Fang-Yi Yu, Grant Schoenebeck and David Kempe In Proceedings of the 23rd ACM Conference on Economics and Computation [https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.09020]

 $(EC \ 2022)$ 

#### Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

Grant Schoenebeck, Fang-Yi Yu and **Yichi Zhang** (ranked by alphabet) In Proceedings of the 30th Annual World Wide Web Conference [https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3442381.3449840]

(WWW 2021)

#### POSTERS

#### Eliciting Effort And Truth-telling From Parties of (No) Interest

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

#### Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

#### A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)
- U-M Asian American Faculty & Student Accomplishments Symposium (2022)

### High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)

#### Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

- DIMACS Workshop on Forecasting (2021)
- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2021)

#### SELECTED TALKS

### Improving Conference Review Via Mechanism Design

• Renmin University of China, Gaoling School of Artificial Intelligence

August 2023

• Peking University, CFCS seminar

July 2023

• University of Michigan, DSCSS seminar

• University of Pennsylvania, Wharton Statistics and Data Science

April 2023 March 2023

#### **TEACHING**

## Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich

Winter 2022

Courses:Big Data Analysis (SI 699)

Instructor: Misha Teplitskiy

## Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich

Fall 2021

Course: Deep Learning (SIADS 642) Instructor: Paramveer Dhillon

Course: Network Analysis (SIADS 642)

Instructor: Daniel Romero

## **AWARDS**

| • The Web Conference Student Scholarship.                         | 2021 |
|-------------------------------------------------------------------|------|
| • Nominee for the Rackham International Student Fellowship, UMSI. | 2021 |
| • Outstanding Graduate of Shanghai Jiao Tong University.          | 2019 |
| • EIC Education Scholarship (top 5%).                             | 2018 |
| • Samsung Scholarship (top 3%).                                   | 2017 |
| • Samsung Scholarship (top 3%).                                   | 2017 |

#### **SERVICE**

# Reviewer/PC member:

• The Web Conference (WWW): 2024, 2023, 2022

• Economics and Computation (EC): 2023, 2022

• Web and Internet Economics (WINE): 2023

Workflow chair: EC 2024